When days turn to weeks...
28 Weeks Later is a horror, thriller, science fiction
film directed by Juan Carlos Fresnadillo.
Twenty-eight weeks after the spread of a deadly rage virus, the inhabitants of the British Isles
have lost their battle against the onslaught, as the virus has killed everyone there.
Six months later, a group of Americans dare to set foot on
the Isles, convinced the danger has passed.
But it soon becomes all too clear that the scourge continues to
live, waiting to pounce on its next victims.
Donald Harris, played by Robert Carlyle.
Scarlet, played by Rose Byrne.
Sergeant Doyle, played by Jeremy Renner.
Flynn, played by Harold Perrineau.
Alice, played by Catherine McCormack.
Andy Harris, played by Mackintosh Muggleton.
28 Weeks Later is a 2007  post-apocalyptic horror film directed by Juan Carlos
Fresnadillo, who co-wrote it with Rowan Joffé, Enrique López Lavigne and Jesus Olmo.
It is the sequel to 28 Days Later (2002) and the
second film in the 28 Days Later series.
The film stars Robert Carlyle, Rose Byrne, Jeremy
Renner, Harold Perrineau, and Idris Elba.
It is set just over six months after the events of the first film, depicting the efforts of United States-led NATO forces to establish a safe zone in London, the
consequence of two young siblings breaking protocol to find a photograph of their mother, and the resulting reintroduction of the rage virus into the safezone.
28 Weeks Later was theatrically released on 11 May 2007 in the United Kingdom and
United States by 20th Century Fox and Fox Atomic, respectively.
It received positive reviews and grossed over $72.3 million worldwide.
A sequel, 28 Years Later, was released on 20 June 2025.
The film explores themes of dying and death, london, england,
sibling relationship, chaos, loss of loved one.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.